If you personally come from a space where you cannot see where I come from personally,
then how would we professionally be able to work together in this particular medium?
There's no way that like racism or oppression or something is never going to come in the room
when I'm working in therapy. It's going to come up because it comes up in my life every day.
And if I'm talking to you about my life every single day in therapy,
you need to feel comfortable discussing that. I shouldn't have to correct you every single time.
I don't want to teach you new words because it also makes me feel like, in my opinion,
clinicians and medical health professionals and stuff like that that aren't anti-racist
shouldn't have their license, right? Because racism should make everyone upset.
Racism is detrimental for everybody. So if you don't know this because you don't educate yourself
outside of the office, I know I shouldn't know about you as a human, but human wise, you kind of suck.